delphipages.com 2010-12-29

# Delphi Pages - Privacy Policy

Delphi Pages Privacy Policy 

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Some of our advertising partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. Please refer to the privacy policies of the network for details [Burst Media](http://www.burstmedia.com/), [Vibrant Media](http://www.vibrantmedia.com/)

**Email-Newsletter List Privacy Policy**   
We maintain a strict "no-spam" policy. If you sign up for any our free newsletter, your e-mail address will not be sold or given to any third party. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we DelphiPages.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
